hello i am finishing out the last track of my album right now my album comes out on sunday
and i wanted to just be vulnerable with y'all real quick so i've been hitting up folks with
podcasts and djs etc just to let them know and to see if i can come on their shows and
there is a piece of me left over from being in hollywood and in the hype yes hurry come over here
if you would like to join the conversation that feels a twinge of corniness hitting up people
directly because the system that's set up is that it has to be a publicist or a manager
or a team and that you know that's what makes what you're doing legit and i'm sharing this because
and yet i still have this feeling and i have to push through it every time because those big
hype contexts are all just gatekeepers to keep everybody apart and to keep folks from feeling
like they aren't legit like their art and their creativity isn't legitimized unless a big commerce
corporate capitalist entity is connected to it the money has to co-sign you for you to be real
and it sucks because that's not true that's not true and as as legit as much of a veteran
as much of an og as much of an established artist creative and person as i am i still feel that
twinge because it's so deep in us so here i am texting folks and let me tell you i'm texting them
which means we have relationships i still feel that pull of like wow you're texting them like yourself
so i just wanted to share that with y'all because it's real and we got to fight and push through it
on both ends we got to see the real work without looking at it through the lens of that which
oppresses us and doesn't even want the real work to get real my album truth translator drops this
sunday june 14th gemini mode head to amandadevanmusic.com to hear the album to support the work through
merch and to find out when i'm going to be in your city with a free sound session this ain't a movement
it's movement music